1
00:00:00,875 --> 00:00:01,710
Oh, my God!

2
00:00:05,171 --> 00:00:05,880
Hang on!

3
00:00:06,297 --> 00:00:08,383
- Ethan!
- Go, go, go!

4
00:00:08,383 --> 00:00:11,761
Audiences and critics can't believe
what they're seeing.

5
00:00:14,139 --> 00:00:15,015
Listen to me.

6
00:00:15,015 --> 00:00:16,850
The world's coming after you.

7
00:00:16,850 --> 00:00:18,101
Stay out of my way.

8
00:00:18,935 --> 00:00:21,187
“Tom Cruise has outdone himself.”

9
00:00:22,105 --> 00:00:25,025
With a 99% on Rotten Tomatoes.

10
00:00:25,025 --> 00:00:25,483
Yes!

11
00:00:25,483 --> 00:00:29,446
“Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning is filled with ‘holy shit’ moments.”

12
00:00:29,446 --> 00:00:30,488
What is happening?

13
00:00:30,488 --> 00:00:32,490
“This is why we go to the movies.”

14
00:00:33,908 --> 00:00:35,577
Oh, I like her.

15
00:00:35,577 --> 00:00:37,287
“It's pulse pounding.”

16
00:00:37,746 --> 00:00:39,622
“It will rock your world.”

17
00:00:40,081 --> 00:00:41,875
With “jaw dropping action.”

18
00:00:43,209 --> 00:00:44,085
Is this where we run?

19
00:00:44,085 --> 00:00:44,919
Go, go, go, go!

20
00:00:45,253 --> 00:00:45,920
Probably.

21
00:00:46,421 --> 00:00:49,132
“It's one of the best action movies
ever made.”

22
00:00:49,466 --> 00:00:50,508
What more can I say?

23
00:00:50,925 --> 00:00:54,888
“See it in the biggest, most seat-shaking theater you can find.”

24
00:00:55,138 --> 00:00:57,891
“It will take your breath away.”

25
00:00:58,808 --> 00:00:59,893
Ethan, did you make it?

26
00:00:59,893 --> 00:01:00,852
Are you okay?

